If you want to make your data available in the long term,
you need to add some metadata to your data
before you can move on to archiving.
Because descriptive metadata is an important aspect
that enables the reuse of your data in the future.
In the FDOrganizer you can add metadata at different levels.
You can specify metadata for your entire project,
as well as for each folder or individual file.
If you want to add metadata at the file level,
first select your package to view the files inside,
then you can use the book symbol next to each file.
If you want to add metadata for the whole project,
use the book symbol next to the projects name.